Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, 1967-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Cassettes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1967-1993, I.; Item 1-149
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 110, after 1984, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Kuala Lumpur #1 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Kuala Lumpur (Malaysia) Derivative files created: 10 (Box 3, Item 110)
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_110_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_110_02-05pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_110_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_110_02-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 111, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Marathon I Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Poor sound quality and a lot of background noise Derivative files created: 18 (Box 3, Item 111)
    Contents: Program begins with Ornstein: Suicide in an airplane; Mikhashoff introduces the works
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_111_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_111_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_111_02-09pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_111_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_111_02-09sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 112, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Marathon III Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 12 (Box 3, Item 112)
    Contents: Unidentified contents but introduced by Mikhashoff
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_112_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_112_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_112_02-07pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_112_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_112_02-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 113, 10 June 1985, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Martland / Sackman Performers: London Sinfonietta, Oliver Knussen, conductor (Martland); unidentified pianist Recording location: Aldeburgh Festival Date and location supplied for likely performance of the Martland work; information about Nicholas Sackman's piano sonata performance lacking Derivative files created: 2 (Box 3, Item 113)
    Contents: Steve Martland: American invention (1985); Sackman: Piano sonata
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_113_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_113_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_113_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_113_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_113_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_113_01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_113_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_113_02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 114, 1972, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Lost Art of Melodeclamation Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Paul Schmidt, voice Recording location: Austin (Texas) Derivative files created: 6 (Box 3, Item 114)
    Contents: Schumann-Shelley: The fugitives; Schubert-Pratobevera: Abschied von der Erde; Liszt-Tolstoy: The blind ministrel; Strauss-Tennyson: Enoch Arden; Poulenc-de Brunhoff: Babar the elephant
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_114_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_114_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_114_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_114_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_114_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_114_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_114_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_114_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_114_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_114_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_114_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_114_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_114_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_114_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 115, 10 November 1990, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: Melodeclamation Buffalo Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Paul Schmidt, voice Recording location: Buffalo (N.Y.) Derivative files created: 8 (Box 3, Item 115)
    Contents: Strauss: Castle by the sea; Schubert: Abschied; Beethoven: Egmont and Lenore Prokaska; Liszt: Mournful music -- Poet's love -- Lenore -- The blind mistrel; Poulenc: Babar
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_115_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_115_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_115_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_115_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_115_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_115_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_115_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_115_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_115_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_115_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_115_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_115_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_115_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_115_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_115_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_115_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_115_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_115_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 116, undated, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Merdella Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 1 (Box 3, Item 116)
    Contents: Merdella: La chasse -- Leandre -- Do nascimiento -- Primire
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_116_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_116_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_116_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 117, 15 September 1991, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Merkin Hall 9/91 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Merkin Hall (New York, N.Y.) Dolby B Entitled: New piano music -- Composer's forum Derivative files created: 3 (Box 3, Item 117)
    Contents: Curran: For Cornelius; Mikhashoff: Shaman: staring through the air; Puccini/Mikhashoff: Aria transcriptions
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_117_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_117_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_117_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_117_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_117_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_117_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_117_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 118, 15 September 1991, 1 DAT cassette; Container title: YM - Merkin Hall Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Merkin Hall (New York, N.Y.) Entitled: New piano music -- Composer's forum; see item 117; this item is a DAT recording Derivative files created: 3 (Box 3, Item 118)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_118_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_118_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_118_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_118_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_118_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_118_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_118_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 119, undated, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: Mexico - Yvar Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Mexico City (Mexico) Derivative files created: 10 (Box 3, Item 119)
    Contents: Thomson; Rzewski: Piano piece no. 4; John Cage: prepared piano piece; Revueltas: piano piece; Ligeti: Etudes; Nancarrow: 5 pieces (on 4 files?)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_119_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_119_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_119_02-07pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_119_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_119_02-07sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 120, 4 February 1983, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Mikhashoff - Sample work #2 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Buffalo (N.Y.) and Copenhagen (Denmark) 2nd work recorded 16 July 1983, Copenhagen; 3rd work recorded 4 February 1983, Buffalo OK Derivative files created: 3 (Box 3, Item 120)
    Contents: Davidovsky: Synchronisms VI; Norgaard: Achilles and the tortoise; Foss: Solo
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_120_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_120_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_120_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_120_01-03pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_120_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_120_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_120_01-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 121, 1972, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Mikhashoff Performers: Richard Field, viola; Amrom Chodos, Allen Sigel, clarinet; Paul Schlossman, oboe Recording location: Unknown locations Dolby; there is voice-over recording at the beginning of Side A that stops within a minute or so Derivative files created: 7 (Box 3, Item 121)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Concerto for viola and orchestra -- Tiento para el espejo de Narciso -- Pipes of Colchis -- Pipes of Colchis -- Partita for solo oboe -- Tiento para el espeja de Narcis
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_121_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_121_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_121_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_121_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_121_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_121_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_121_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_121_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_121_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_121_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_121_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_121_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_121_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_121_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_121_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_121_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 122, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Mikhashoff "Earth Spirit"; Smalley PF. CTO Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; unknown others Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 2 (Box 3, Item 122)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Concerto for viola and orchestra; Smalley: Piano concerto
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_122_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_122_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_122_01-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_122_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_122_01-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 123, 2 October 1985, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: David Campbell, clarinet, Mikhashoff Night dances Performers: David Campbell, clarinet; Andrew Ball, piano; BBC Concert Orchestra, James Lockhart, conductor Recording location: London (England) Recording date from BBC broadcast; date of Mikhashoff performance unknown OK Derivative files created: 5 (Box 3, Item 123)
    Contents: Florent Schmitt: Andantino; Bush: Rhapsody; Waterson: Morceau de concert; Side B. Spoken introduction by Mikhashoff; Mikhashoff: Night dances
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_123_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_123_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_123_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_123_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_123_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_123_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_123_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_123_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_123_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_123_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_123_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_123_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 124, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Mikhashoff Performers: Unidentified chamber ensemble Recording location: Unknown location OK Derivative files created: 2 (Box 3, Item 124)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Windwife (two versions)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_124_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_124_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_124_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_124_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_124_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_124_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 125, 6 August 1983, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Light from a distant garden: Mikhashoff Performers: Carl Nielsen Kvartetten Recording location: Lerchenborg (Denmark) World premiere OK Derivative files created: 1 (Box 3, Item 125)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Light from a distant garden (Deploration in memoriam Poul Rovsing Olsen)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_125_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_125_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_125_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 126, 19 November 1978, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Dances for Davia Performers: Unknown flutist; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Other names on cassette label: [Arthur] Ephross, [David?] Fallis; O'Hallacan? OK Derivative files created: 1 (Box 3, Item 126)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Dances for Davia
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_126_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_126_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_126_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 127, 14 November 1989, 1 100 minute cassette; Container title: Yvar recital Nov. '89 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University at Buffalo, Slee Hall From concert titled Music from Paris (1839-1989) 02-02 is Chopin Derivative files created: 17 (Box 3, Item 127)
    Contents: Debussy: Prelude. La puerta del vino -- Feuilles mortes -- Ce qu'a vu le vent d'ouest -- Images, 2nd series -- Prelude. Ondine; Ravel: Gaspard de la nuit. Ondine; Debussy: La serenade interrompue; Ravel: Miroirs. Alborado del gracioso; Chopin: Nocturne op.32 no.1 -- Nocturne op.55 no.2; Debussy: Etudes pour les arpeges composes -- Etude pour les huits doigts; Liszt: Les Jeux d'eau a la Villa d'Este no.4 -- Nuages gris -- Rhapsodie hongroise no.19 (arr. Mikhashoff)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_127_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_127_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_127_02-10pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_127_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_127_02-10sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 128, 18 September 1988, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Rehearsal: Flowers for Joan Mitchell Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Robert Schultz, percussion; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Buffalo, N.Y.) Date and place based on concert performance of 18 September 1988 OK Derivative files created: 2 (Box 3, Item 128)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Flowers for Joan Mitchell
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_128_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_128_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_128_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_128_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_128_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_128_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 129, 22 May 1992 - 25 May 1992, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Ten Yvar tangos Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby B This contains nothing but background noise, no music Derivative files created: 1 (Box 3, Item 129)
    Contents: Rudhyar: Tango d'Antan; Biscardi: Incitation to desire; Duckworth: Tango voices; Pender: Ms. Jackson dances...; Genge: Tango for Yvar; Foss: Tango; Nancarrow; Sahl: Exile's Café; Berkman: Thorn torn lips; Hill: Tango no tango
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_129_01am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_129_01-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_129_01-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 130, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Elemental figures Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 2 (Box 3, Item 130)
    Contents: Mikhashoff rehearsing passages from his composition Elemental figures
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_130_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_130_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_130_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_130_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_130_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_130_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 131, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Elemental figures Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Derivative files created: 6 (Box 3, Item 131)
    Contents: Unidentified contents that may include Mikhashoff's Elemental figures
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_131_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_131_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_131_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_131_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_131_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_131_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_131_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_131_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_131_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_131_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_131_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_131_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_131_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_131_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 132, 7 December 1988, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: Elemental figures Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Note: Mikhashoff was scheduled to perform in Miami at the New Music America Festival 7 December 1988 Derivative files created: 2 (Box 3, Item 132)
    Contents: Possible rehearsal of Mikhashoff's composition Elemental figures
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_132_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_132_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_132_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_132_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_132_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_132_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 133, undated, 1 90 minute cassette; Container title: Elemental figures; On label: Ondine/Sibyl fragments Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Dolby Derivative files created: 21 (Box 3, Item 133)
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_133_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_133_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-10pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-11pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-12pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-13pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-14pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-15pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_133_02-16pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_133_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-10sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-11sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-12sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-13sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-14sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-15sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_133_02-16sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 134, 13 August 1991 - 15 August 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: August sessions #1 of 4 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby B reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician. Tapes 134-150 were from recording sessions for content published on Mode Records Panorama of American Piano Music (2013). Derivative files created: 6 (Box 3, Item 134)
    Contents: Recording session of solo piano works by Morton Feldman, including Intermission 5, Piano piece 1952, Extensions 3, Piano piece 1956a, and more
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_134_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_134_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_134_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_134_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_134_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_134_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_134_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_134_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy files: ubmu0001_6_134_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_134_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_134_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_134_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_134_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_6_134_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Audio Cassettes, Tape 135, 13 August 1991 - 15 August 1991, 1 60 minute cassette; Container title: August sessions #2 of 4 Performers: Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Slee Hall, University at Buffalo Dolby B reference copy of DAT master; includes multiple full and partial takes with announcements of works by studio technician Derivative files created: 9 (Box 3, Item 135)
    Contents: Recording session of works, including Copland: Three sonnets; Nancarrow: Blues; Stravinsky: Valse pour les enfants; Riegger: Blue voyage; Rudhyar: Pentagram no. 3. Stars
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_6_135_01am.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_02am.wav
    Production master files: ubmu0001_6_135_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_02-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_6_135_02-06pm.wav